迈克 · 诺斯: 这个，虽然我不知道该怎么说，但我还是想告诉你
&gt;&gt; Mike North: This, I kinda feel
abrogated to show you this although I
我没有发现我经常使用抽象类。
don't find that I use it all that often,
abstract classes.
抽象类不能直接实例化，它们只是作为基类。
Abstract classes cannot be instantiated
directly, they just serve as base classes.
所以不像在接口中，它也不能实例化,
So unlike in interface,
which also can't be instantiated,
抽象类可以有实现，对吗？
abstract classes can have implementations,
right?
在本例中，我有一个带有一些 param 属性的构造函数，因此 name 和
In this case, I have a constructor with
some param properties ,so name and
电子邮件会在那里，它的服务作为一个基本类。
email will be there,
it's serving as a base class.
但是我也有一个抽象的方法
But I also have an abstract method here,
and
必须由任何子类实现。
that must be implemented by any subclass.
所以我认为这是一种半类半接口的方式。
So I think of this as sort of half class,
half interface.
这样我们就可以四处传阅了。
And this lets us pass around.
我们仍然可以通过它们的抽象基类引用两个事物。
We can still refer two things
by their abstract base class.
但具体的实现可能看起来非常非常不同。
But concrete implementations
may look very, very different.
在这里你所要做的就是把类抽象化
All you have to do here is
make the class abstract and
然后你可以把字段和方法都抽象化。
then you can make both fields and
methods abstract as well.
因此需要类来实现具有兼容访问修饰符的类。
And so classes are required to implement
those with a compatible access modifier.
比如，你可以拿一些受保护的东西，我想知道你是否可以这样做。
Like, you could take something protected,
I wonder if you can even do that.
迈克 · 诺斯: 是的。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: Yep.
迈克 · 诺斯: 不，看起来他们已经修好了这里。
&gt;&gt; Mike North: No, it looks like
that they've fixed this here.
所以必须把事情公开，因为抽象有点奇怪
So gotta make things public because
it'd be kinda strange to have abstract
一些私人的事情，比如怎么做？
things that are private, like how?
这样你就不能真正了解子类了。
You don't really have visibility
into subclasses in that way.
这是一个实现的例子，你可以看到,
So here's an example of an implementation,
and you can see,
如果我们移除 sendEmail 它会告诉我们,
if we were to remove sendEmail,
it's gonna tell us,
非抽象类 ConcreteContact 不实现
non-abstract class,
ConcreteContact, does not implement
继承的继承抽象成员 sendEmail。
inherited inherited
abstract member sendEmail.
因此，我们还没有达到我们需要满足的所有要求。
So we have not met all of
the requirements we need to meet.